{"data":[{"question":"There are twenty species of wild roses in North America, all of which have prickly stems, pinnate leaves, and large flowers, which usually smell ________.","a":"sweetly","b":"sweet","c":"sweetness","d":"sweetish","answer":"2","explain":"- Adjectives often goes after smell","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Having ________ the topics for their essays, the students were instructed to make either a preliminary outline or a rough draft.","a":"chose","b":"chosen","c":"choose","d":"choice","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use past participle form( having+ pp) in place of After\/As soon as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Gilbert Stuart is considered by most art critics ________ greatest portrait painter in the North American colonies.","a":"that he was","b":"as he was","c":"who was the","d":"the","answer":"4","explain":"\n- We use the superlative of short adjectives(great)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"As a safety measure, the detonator for a nuclear device may be made of ________, each of which is controlled by a different employee.","a":"two equipments","b":"two pieces of equipments","c":"two pieces of equipment","d":"two equipment pieces","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be made of something","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"An equilateral triangle is a triangle ________ and three angles of equal size.","a":"that have three sides of equal length","b":"it has three sides equally long","c":"that has three sides of equal length","d":"having three equal length sides in it","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use the relative clause with That\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Some students set confused ________ having to suffer long and hard years before they attain any level of success.","a":"with","b":"in","c":"about","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Confused about + V-ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"________ are found on the surface of the moon.","a":"Craters and waterless seas that","b":"When craters and waterless seas","c":"Craters and waterless seas","d":"Since craters and waterless seas","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We need the subject to make a complete sentence","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"His ________ made him cry.","a":"fearful","b":"fearfulness","c":"fearless","d":"fearlessness","answer":"2","explain":"\n- His: used as the possessive adjective followed a noun","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"________ two waves pass a given point simultaneously, they will have no effect on each other's subsequent motion.","a":"So that","b":"They are","c":"That","d":"If","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"A child in the first grade tends to be ________ all of the other children in the class.","a":"the same old to","b":"the same age than","c":"as old like","d":"the same age as","answer":"4","explain":"\n-The same + Noun + as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}